ubookmarking.com 2011-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Ubookmarking

We value our website visitors and customers, personal privacy of our customers and website visitors is our priority. The following information provides disclosures about our information use and gathering and practices for the Ubookmarking.com website.

**Our Privacy Ideology**

* We never sell or trade the information about our customers. * We never provide our customers’ information to third party organizations or individuals. * Customers’ information collected is solely used for marketing and business development purposes of Ubookmarking.com

**Collection of Information**

The information that we collect is indented for our internal use, business development, marketing development, service improvement, and customer service improvement. Ubookmarking.com might collect and keep certain kinds of customer information that is needed for these purposes; this information can be full name, residential or business address, work or home phone numbers, and current email address. In addition , when visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and analyze only the following information about you: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; referring domains and search engines; the locations of such referring domains; visits (new and returning); number of pages viewed per visit. We use this information for statistical and analytical purposes. We do not collect and require any personal information about you through this website, however if it was provided voluntary we might keep it and use it for the stated purposes.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain certain links to other sites for customer convenience. Ubookmarking.com is not responsible for privacy practices of other websites. It is highly recommended to check the privacy policy on each website and use your own discretion about giving out your information on different websites.

**Changes of Privacy Policy**

Ubookmarking.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting an update. Changes to our privacy policy will be effective as soon as they are posted. Visitors should review our privacy policy periodically so they are aware of different changes by which they are bound. If you have any questions, comments or suggestions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your experience with this website, please E-mail us at info@ubookmarking.com
